MUHAMMAD ANAS AFZAAL

B-185 Saghir Centre, Block-16 F.B Area, Karachi.

Phone: +(92)312 3616359 Email: anaskhan.all95@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer - Aimviz (March 2022 - Present)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of Web Applications.

Technologies & Skills: Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, ASP.Net Core Web API, MSSQL, C#, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap.

Front end Developer – Symits (September 2020 – February 2022)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of static and dynamic websites.

Technologies & Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, WordPress, Shopify and, Adobe Photoshop.

Front end Developer – Optimal Creations (March 2020 –

August 2020)

Responsibilities: Development, optimization, and, maintenance of static and dynamic websites and content writing for websites and social media marketing.

Technologies & Skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, WordPress, Shopify.

EDUCATION

- Masters of Computer Science (MCS) University of Karachi
 (2021– Present)
- ➤ Bachelors of Computer Science (BCS) University of Karachi (2016 2019)
- ➤ Intermediate (Pre-Engineering) D.J Science College (2012 2014)
- ➤ Matriculation (Computer Science) Metropolitan Academy (2000 2012)

SUMMARY

I am a professional Software Developer having core expertise in the latest technologies and trends such as JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, React, C#, ASP.Net Core, ASP.Net Core Web API, MS SQL, jQuery, HTML and CSS to name a few.

LINKS

Portfolio

LinkedIn.

SKILLS

lavaScript:	_
Angular:	
TypeScript:	
Query:	
C#:	
SQL:	
Git:	
HTML:	
CSS:	
SCSS:	
ASP.NET:	
VordPress:	
Poact.	